Hey everyone! I don't know if I should start every video like that, I try not to, but the reason for
the video is that you used my Amoresi coat a lot, my discount coat, which you can find here. So I
thought you might be interested in seeing more of Amoresi outfits and I got a new box. I'm going to
show you mix and match combinations of bodysuits and tights today. Really, really colorful. Oh and
And since the video is focusing on bodysuits and tights today, I'm wearing a catsuit for
a start, also by Amorese.
So let's just dive into it and start right away.
This is the first combination of tights and bodysuit and I have various colors I'm going
to show you afterwards.
But first I want to talk to you about the bodysuits.
This one is a bodysuit with a normal leg cutout.
As you can see from behind, like a normal cut.
Ameliezi also offers bodysuits with high leg cutouts. So now this is the high
cutout version with a string part in the back. Oops sorry. This is right. I fall over it
so often. I think if a person is like 10-15 centimeters smaller than I am you
would not see skin here. That's why I prefer the low cut bodysuits because it
overlaps the leggings better and I'm just like too tall here so this one rides up
and the leggings can't cover everything up but I like the back I think it's cool
to wear this kind of colors together especially with the black heels here but
with all the combinations I'm going to show you now no heels just the socks or
Soul to soul, please hold my hand
We will jump off from a cliff
We are flying without wings
Silver lining crazy dreams
You whisper I love you in my ear
While we are jumping from a cliff
We are walls of the moon
The bloody lake of our love
Crazy walls of the moon
So these have just been a few of the nearly endless combinations you can do with the tights
and bodysuits.
I've also shown you a swimsuit and this one is a swimsuit as well and I love the
combination of black and red with the white I think the white makes the black
and red really pop. For the backside it's not ideal with the leggings also not
with the bra but hey we're on YouTube and just ignore the backside you would
have to wear without tights and bra because then it has a really nice
I spray a back swimsuit which I really like but from the front it's also okay I guess.
I'm only going to link the articles in the description text not every color
because that would be too much and you should just have a look at the Amorese
homepage and click through all the different colors they are launching new
colors on a regular basis so keep an eye on that homepage of course you will also
find my discount code in the description text and you will find pictures that
of for example this outfit on my patreon so check that out as well. For the last
outfit I'm going to change into a swimsuit combination without leggings
this time. Actually this is a two-piece set so you have the panty and the
bodysuit on top so it is kind of mix and match again because of course you could
wear the swimsuit without the panty but I think this is like a unique design to
have this really really extra high cut here that wants to show some skin here
this time and the panty that matches the color and this is the back side view I
think it really makes a great bum without showing the bum too much or
without being nude that is a really cool feature and I love the cutout detail
here in the shoulder because although it is a rather plain top it adds something
extra and special here and I think the overall design is rather unique I have
not seen many swimsuits like that I'm surprised about the green color because
I think it looks okay although I'm not the biggest fan of green but yeah I
think that looks really cool together I just think cool the whole time I have to
find another word send me suggestions for other words than cool in the
comments please and while you're at it also like the videos subscribe to my
channel and thanks for your attention today check out my discount code and
I'll see you in the next video bye